So, Mark, as part of my work, I've spent
a lot of time talking to developers and
trying to understand how their behaviors
and workflows are changing as agents
become more of a
centerpiece [music] to their work. Um
and the main thing that I keep hearing
is skills.
Skills are great to gather context and
to manage context and to help developers
have a [music] bit of control around the
agent's output and execution of tasks.
Um but the conversation shifts a bit
when developers start to think about
sharing those skills
uh with the organizations and the the
rest of the team members. The question
becomes, is this skill actually any
good? [music] Is it helping my agents
succeed with their tasks? So, what would
you say is the easiest way for
developers to gain some confidence
around the skills they're building so
they can share them more broadly?
The easiest way for developers to gain
confidence in the skills they're
building is to use Tessel's skill
optimizer plugin.
It's really easy for them to get
started. They go to tessel.io/registry,
search for skill optimizer,
copy and paste the command to install
Tessel and the skill optimizer plugin
into their terminal,
and then it's a case of firing up their
favorite agent and asking it to optimize
their skill.
What the plugin does is it takes a look
at the skill and figures out the best
way to evaluate its quality.
It evaluates its quality
and then uses the feedback from that to
figure out how the skill can be
improved. It works with the user to make
those changes and then it runs the whole
thing again to understand whether those
changes made a positive difference.
The idea is that the plugin assists the
agent throughout and automates as much
of the flow as possible
and helps developers get from wondering
if their skill is good enough to share
to knowing that their skill is good
enough to share. And that's a really key
question. You're bringing up the the
word good and what good means.
Um and that can mean different things
depending [music] on the situation and
the developer you're talking to. So,
what I've heard from my conversations
with the butter apples is that good
means it follows best practices. It's
well written. It can also mean it
activates at the right time when it's
needed by [music] the agent. And it also
contributes to success of a task
execution. So, what's under this the
hood of the skill optimizer that can
help address these pain points?
So, the skill optimizer plugin is
actually a bundle of different skills
[music] that have been designed to work
with Tessell's powerful evaluation CLI
tool kit.
And as you mentioned, there are
different ways to look at skill quality.
So, we have various tools to help with
different uh aspects of that. For
example, our skill review looks at the
content of the skill to understand
whether it follows Anthropic's
principles of best practice.
This is useful in a quick feedback loop
where developers are actively working on
the skill and want to make sure it's in
the best shape. But it doesn't tell them
much about how the skill actually
performs. So, we have a separate type of
evaluation where we run the skill
against realistic scenarios in a
simulation sandbox to check how the
skill actually performs and if it does
what it's meant to do.
We've also recently added a new type of
evaluation to see for those realistic
scenarios if the agent natively chooses
that skill to run in those scenarios.
And this is a way to measure what
activation of a skill might look like in
real-world situations.
So, really the skill optimizer [music]
helps developers cover all these pain
points and
take us to a world where developers have
the confidence [music] to share the
skills with others. Um in this world,
this new world where there's more people
in the organization [music] using the
same skills, another concern raises, uh
which is how do you make sure that
skills [music] stay alive and they don't
go stale? Yeah, this is a problem that
Tessell has itself with the skill
optimizer plugin. As you can imagine,
our toolkit is constantly evolving and
improving and every time it does, we
need to make sure the skill optimizer
plugin is up to date with the latest.
So, we actually run skill optimizer on
the skills in the skill optimizer plugin
and that's a great way to make sure that
it is always
up-to-date and has high quality.
But, we've also integrated many of
Tessel's CLI commands into our CICD
workflow as a way for us to catch
regressions [music] on changes that are
made to our skill files
as and when they are made.
This is useful for ensuring that skills,
not just customer-facing skills, like
the skill optimizer plugin, but also
internal skills that the developer team
use are always at the highest standard
of quality and these tools are available
to all of our customers as well.
Amazing. So, how do they get started?
It's really easy. If you visit
tessel.io/registry,
search for skills optimizer,
select the Tessel skills optimizer
plugin,
then you'll see a command that you can
copy and paste into your CLI terminal
and this will install both Tessel and
the skill optimizer plugin in one go.
Once that's installed, it's as simple as
firing up your favorite agent and asking
it to optimize a skill.
Simple enough. Thanks for sharing, Mark.
No problem.
So, remember, visit tessel.io/registry,
search for skills optimizer and get
started on your skill optimization
journey today.